spambotsecurity.com 2014-12-15

# Privacy Policy | SpambotSecurity.com

## Spambot Security.com's  
Site Privacy Policy

### CAVEAT: Usage of this site veritably guarantees some of your information, will be disclosed to me, and some third parties.

That said, read on if you like...

###  Our Commitment to Your Privacy

Your privacy is important to SpambotSecurity.com. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on these pages and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

### The Information We Collect 

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the SpambotSecurity.com website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials or make use of our private forums. The types of personal information collected at these pages may be any or all of the following: 

Name  
Address  
Phone Number  
Email Address  
IP Address (required for use on our private forum)  
Credit/Debit Card Information

The credit and payment services we utilize to process your order have their own privacy statements which may be different from those found here at SpambotSecurity.com. It is therefore recommended that you carefully read the privacy statements located on these other sites to help protect your privacy. 

### How We Use Your Information 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive, to send verifications for membership in our foums, and to send notifications regarding services. Such addresses are not shared with outside parties or sold. 

You can subscribe to posts in our forums if you would like to receive updates on new messages through e-mail.

We use the revenue generating services of Google Adsense on this site, and do no collection of user information for the sake of said advertising at this site, however, google may do so on their system. See [_http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html_](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) for information on Google's policies regarding this.

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.   
* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.   
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [_Google ad and content network privacy policy_](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

However, if your use of this website entailed hostile actions, or you are attempting access from a banned IP address or Domain name, your attempt will be publicly logged. The information displayed in this log includes, but is not limited to...

Date and time of attempt.  
Your hostname.  
Your IP Address.  
How many security triggers your attempt set off.  
Why your attempt was blocked.  
Contents of your HTTP_POST data.  
Contents of your URL query.  
Your referrer information.  
and Your User-Agent information.

### Our Commitment to Your Data Security 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. However, in the face of ever more hostile attacks upon websites worldwide, you should not construe this as a guarantee of security.

### Our Commitment to Children's Privacy 

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important to us at SpambotSecurity.com. And for that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under the age of 13. No part of our website is structured to attract anyone under the age of 13. 

Also, if we hear of, are informed of, or are witness to any illegal activity with, to, or directed at children, we will promptly report such parties to the proper authorities for prosecution.
